Updates are very very important on your device but sometimes the same update can cause issues
on your Windows server or Windows client device so if I go to for example if I go to my start
menu and I type update here I can go to Windows update settings so let me just click on
Windows update settings so on our Windows update set is there you can see we have Windows
updates and now you can see we have some available updates which are actually ready to install
so we can actually view updates history so let's just go to this history here you can see we
have some definition updates other updates and driver updates which have been successful
installed on this device but if you're having a situation where buying a specific update is
causing for example I am constantly your Windows server to restart or Windows client and you
went to a friend field and you realize that that specific update you install was the update
responsible for causing your device to crash or to restart what you can do is for example you
can see we have on our view update history we have on install updates so by clicking on
install update is going to take me to programs and future here you can see we have the installed
update and on our store update you can see we have some updates which can be installed
and not all the updates can actually be installed so others you need to use but for example
the partial script to uninstall that update so here you can see we have for example we have the
update for Microsoft Windows and that is the knowledge base of that update has a KB so if I click
on that you can see I have the option to uninstall also have for example service impact you can see
I don't even have the option to uninstall service impact and if I click this updates and you can see
not all updates can actually be on install from this device so let's say you have some update
that didn't install or some updates could not be installed what you can actually do is you can
now if I open services and just click on services so let me just expand that and if I go to
standard and here I can just search for windows you can see we have the windows update which
I just wanted to run in sometimes if you try to search from updates and you couldn't found any
updates what you could do is to start your windows update service so because by when your windows
of this service is stopped you couldn't the updates could not be downloaded or installed on your
device so by restarting that service then if the service is stopped or we can also restart
the service so I totally force every update that is actually being that needs to be installed
and also we have if I go to advanced options you can see it says give me updates for all our
Microsoft for that when I update windows we can totally that is actually you can actually turn
it on what is from when it's a total turn of it's automatic download of this even over mated data
connection this applies to your windows 10 or windows 11 device because your windows service
mostly connected to wired network connection and multi-wifi connection our namasana company
that connects the domain control our windows server to your wifi connection so let me just go back
again and here you can see we can decide right now to just click install to start installing
all the necessary updates on this device